so here is an alternative definition of
所以这是对
Asian games that is essentially
从本质上讲，亚洲运动会
identical mathematically but presented
数学上相同但呈现
differently it's based on types or more
根据类型或更多而不同
fully epistemic types and the type of
完全认识的类型和类型
the agent is supposed to capture
该代理应该捕获
everything that's private information to
所有的私人信息
the agents so if you look at you know
代理商，所以如果你看着你知道
the first definition of Asian game that
亚洲游戏的第一个定义是
we saw having to do with certainty about
我们看到与确定有关
types and the common pryor then the type
类型和普通的pryor然后类型
of the agent was her private signal that
她的私人信号是
is the information set in which the the
是其中的信息集
get chosen game lies as well as
被选择的游戏谎言以及
everything that emanates from it namely
由此产生的一切
her beliefs about what the possible
她对可能的信念
information of the other agents are and
其他代理商的信息是和
information of the other agent about
其他代理商的有关信息
yourself and so forth so all of that is
自己等等，所有这些都是
folded into the notion of a type so
折叠成一个类型的概念
that's mathematically very convenient
从数学上讲这很方便
packing all this information into a type
将所有这些信息打包成一个类型
formally speaking then the Bayesian game
正式来说贝叶斯博弈
is defined as follows it's defined as
定义如下
this tuple that is as follows we have a
这个元组如下
set of agents we have the actions
我们有行动的代理人集合
available to the agent so now we don't
提供给代理商，所以现在我们不
have sets of games we have very directly
有几组游戏我们非常直接
the actions available to the agent and
代理可用的操作和
now we have the type this abstract
现在我们有这个抽象的类型
mathematical object that care that
关心那个的数学对象
captures the private information of the
捕获的私人信息
agents so we have a type for each agent
代理商，所以我们为每个代理商都有一个类型
and we have a common prior as B as in
我们有一个共同的先验B
the first definition of games we have a
游戏的第一个定义是
common prior but now it's not over games
以前很常见，但现在还没有结束
it's over types so agent each agent had
这是类型，所以每个代理都有代理
the type and that prior is common the
类型和先验是常见的
type is chosen according to a
类型根据选择
probability distribution that's commonly
通常的概率分布
known by all the agents and each agent
所有代理商和每个代理商都知道
knows
知道
type therefore they also have a
因此，他们也有一个
posterior about the type of the other
关于其他类型的后验
agents and beliefs about what the other
代理人和其他人的信念
agents might believe it about their own
特工可能会相信自己
type and so on and so forth this is the
类型，依此类推，这就是
type of the agents and we have the
代理商的类型，我们有
utility function now depend not only are
实用功能现在不仅取决于
the actions taken by the agents but of
代理商采取的行动，但
their type that's the formal definition
他们的类型就是正式定义
again it's mathematically in something
再次从数学上讲
very simple but the intuition is
很简单，但直觉是
complicated because the notion of a type
复杂，因为类型的概念
packs into it a lot of things so let's
包装了很多东西，所以让我们
see it in action
看到它在行动
consider this game that we saw when we
考虑一下我们看到的这个游戏
discussed the first definition of
讨论了第一个定义
evasion games again we had four possible
再次进行回避游戏，我们有四种可能
games being played chosen by at random
随机选择的正在玩的游戏
by nature according to this prior and we
根据这个先天的本质，我们
all we had the private signals that the
我们所有的私人信号都表明
information sets that the agents found
代理商发现的信息集
themselves in here is the type
自己在这里是类型
perspective on this so what are the
对此的观点是什么
actions available to agents very simply
代理可以轻松执行的操作
the row agent has the up or down action
行代理具有向上或向下操作
actions and the column agents have the
操作和列代理具有
left-to-right actions that pay off
从左到右的行动有回报
however will depend on their type so
但是将取决于它们的类型，所以
let's let's look for example what
让我们来看例如
happens here so what is the payoff when
发生在这里，那么什么是回报
the agent the raw agent plays up and the
代理，原始代理出现，并且
column player plays lift well that
专栏运动员发挥良好，
depends if the type of the agents is
取决于代理商的类型是
this one or what is the type the type
这一种还是什么类型
corresponds now to this information that
现在对应于该信息，
they have and the type of the second
他们有和第二种
player is this well what the path then
玩家好在那走什么路
well the path corresponds now to this
路径现在与此对应
cell right there
那里的细胞
is what happens when they play up and
当他们玩耍时会发生什么
left and so you get 2 and 0 when the
左，所以当得到2和0时
types are as they are let's take some
类型是一样，让我们​​来一些
other random example here is clear the
其他随机示例在这里很明显
slide let's take some rather rather
幻灯片让我们采取一些宁可
example here clearing the slide and let
这里的示例清除幻灯片，然后让
us look for example at down and left
我们看一下向下和向左
when the types are these well what is
当这些类型很好的时候
the what are the what what are the what
什么是什么什么是什么
are the types so the type is sick is
是类型，所以类型是生病的是
this one right here so the this is the
这个就在这里，这是
information available to the first agent
第一代理人可获得的信息
the second agent has this information
第二个代理商有此信息
available to her which means that this
向她提供这意味着
right here is the game being played and
在这里是正在玩的游戏，
what is DL DL means that we're playing
DL DL是什么意思我们在玩
down and lifts there will be this one
向下并举起会有这个
and therefore the payoff will be
因此，回报将是
correspondingly 0 and 0 so you can look
分别对应0和0，所以您可以看一下
at other examples and figure out what
在其他例子中，找出什么
the type based formulation means by just
基于类型的表述意味着
taking some random row here and figuring
在这里采取一些随机行并计算
out why the row is the way it is the
找出为什么行是这样的
last thing to say here before we move on
在我们继续之前要在这里说的最后一件事
to analysis is that in this particular
要分析的是
example by fixing the type you ended up
通过修复最终类型的示例
with a very specific game and this is a
一个非常具体的游戏，这是一个
complicated topic where in fact if you
复杂的话题实际上，如果您
wanted to map it uncertainty over games
想将不确定性映射到游戏上
you may not have unique game and you
您可能没有独特的游戏，而您
need to look at the set of games and the
需要看一组游戏和
expectation there
那里的期望
but I'm just flanging this as a topic
但我只是把它当作主题
what we discussed will give you a good
我们讨论的内容将为您带来好处
handle on the two formulations of
处理以下两个公式
Bayesian games the explicit from a
贝叶斯游戏从
listing of games and a common prior over
游戏清单和共同的优先权
them and a partition structure for the
他们和一个分区结构
agents or the type based formulation
剂或基于类型的配方